Where there was not God's folk, then there was.
to Life is your word episode three.
this show, we build up our understanding of reality by seeking God's
face.
reading is from Genesis chapter one.
God began to create the heavens and the earth, earth was in complete
chaos and darkness covered the face of the
Jeep.
over the face of the waters,
God said, let there be light and there was light.
God saw that
light was good and God separated the light from the darkness.
created humans in the image of God.
blessed them, saying be fruitful and fill the earth.
have given you everything. my past death, lived in complete
chaos and the great darkness of
depression covered
I tried to run my race in my strength
I tried
than by Christ living in me.
God's, then God spoke and I became.
filled me. Peace beyond human understanding.
I became compelled to shout God's praise from every mountain top
and share God's great works with everyone.
I thank God regularly for my role in partaking in creation
as I create these
as God created all things for our benefit.
reminds me that nothing is impossible through Christ who gives me
The one who speaks all things into being can transform the one who
death have you lived?
your revelations in the comments. love and unity, Ace of El.
Welcome to Life is your word episode three. In this show, we build
up our understanding of reality by seeking
God's face. Today's reading is from Genesis chapter one. When God
began to create the heavens and the earth,
the earth was in complete chaos
and darkness covered the face of the Jeep.
While a wind of God, swept over the face of the
waters,
then God said, let there be light and there was
light. And God saw that
the light was good
and God separated the light from the
darkness. God created humans in the image of God.
God blessed them,
saying be fruitful and fill the earth.
I have given you everything. In my past death,
I lived in complete chaos and
the great darkness of depression covered
my face. I stopped listening to God's voice
and I tried
rather than by Christ living in me.
But God's, but then God spoke
and I became. Life filled me.
Peace beyond human understanding. Joy that defied world the authorities.
And I became compelled to shout God's praise from every
mountain top and share God's great works with everyone.
So I thank God regularly for my role in
partaking in creation as I create these things for your
benefit just as God created all things for our
benefit.
This
This reminds me that nothing is impossible through Christ
who gives me
the one who
your life too. What death have you
And how does he speak you into being and life? Share your revelations in
the comments.
In love and unity, Ace of El.